I'm telling you I need I need uh yoga I
try to take yoga take hot yoga my
friend's like you remember I was all
hunched over started taking
yoga completely straight there was a guy
in hot yoga had no arm started taking
yoga new Arm coming in it's skinny but
it's coming in you got to try it you'd
relax so I'm in there and first of all
it's 140° I I see Satan he's like this
is too
much so I'm trying and and they try not
to get you and there was an anorexic up
front there was nothing left to her
except like a yoga suit and a puddle of
water okay so the so the the guyy is
saying okay it's very important that you
don't leave the room uh and it's oh and
it smelled like an uncleaned monkey cage
after 6 months they left that out okay
it's very important that you don't leave
the room now you might experience
fainting absolutely
normal my heart's trying to go like
pitter patter right um You might
actually do some of of the positions and
sever your own spinal cord this is
correct this is correct this is great
devotion uh you might feel your right
arm go numb as you go into the next
lifetime um it's an Indian um practice
so we keep the circle of life just keeps
going okay so it's very important that
you don't take use Leave the Room which
is why I've taken the key and I throw it
it out the window so we're going to
start with praana breathing so I tried
that I mean everyone the only people
that last are like are gay guys and
women cuz we know how to suffer to look
good okay there was a there was a Navy
SEAL going water boarding was easier
than
this so anyway I tried that and then I
took a now there's one accent I'm not
crazy about do we have any people from
La H good okay cuz I learned how to
drive in LA and I didn't know that some
guy Mook me for like a you know like a
they stamped your ticket in a restaurant
he he thought I was the hostess and um
he's like can you validate me I didn't
even know what that meant I'm like
you're warm you're loving you know how
stupid I
felt so they don't so I'm in it so the
woman's like oh yeah it's really nice to
be here I'm the I'm going to be the
substitute teacher
yeah already I'm getting angry right
sweating I'm like
this I'm like it's inhale and
exhale inhale exhale I was so I had to
take another yoga class just to calm
down from that yoga
class so I take the guide of meditation
as you can see anyone meditation here
it's
really nothing just you you nothing
you're just smiling
away you're just happy and life just
what about you sir what do you
do no
exercise great see guys don't care no
exercise I put on 300 pounds I'm a guy I
don't care you know you live you die I'm
G to eat everything on that menu tonight
I don't care I really don't care I took
I love deepo Chopra I I love him and
he's and he's like and I tried to listen
to him he's like you are part of
nothingness and nothingness is part of
nothing of something and something is
part of nothing but you are part of
Nothing Even though you are part of
something and the universe is part of
nothingness I'm like what's what's she
talking about I'm getting tense now I
feel like a loser on a cosmic
level so I'm like let me listen to a
little less esoteric yoga she's like
breathe in and breathe out and release
all of your anxieties like anxieties
that's not a word didn't someone check
her phonetic English I mean I'm sure
she's brilliant anties breathe in from
your head down to your uncle uncle I
don't want to think about my uncle I
want to
relax so I thought let me go to a
British guided meditation you know I
could listen to it I follow along nice
accent it's like you're in a lovely
field you you see trees you see a
unicorn slowly coming towards you and
the Unicorn carries a sacred chant in
its mouth now for a small fee the chant
will be
yours just go to www. britt.com
and please hit
subscribe so I thought you know what I
need a New York guide to meditation it's
honest it's relatable I can follow along
breathe in and breathe out and hold your
breath cuz the dog just poed in the
park breathe in and breathe out you're
going to hear the Clank in a bottles
that's the homeless they need your don't
judge leisy be judge Karma
baby breathe in and breathe out I don't
want you to think about your W batwing
arms your flabby thighs or your horrible
children one day they'll have children
that will be horrible to them and you
will know profound I repeat profound
Joy breathe in and breathe out I don't
want you to think about your emotionally
unavailable partner that never takes you
out because everyone in New York City is
gay breathe in and breathe out and
remember the upper and lower levels of
the George Washington Bridge is going to
be closed
indefinitely and breathe in and please
close your eyes not for any Serenity but
the guide of the right of me is wearing
a space helmet and nothing else
on thank you now listen hasn't the world
gotten incredibly
greedy like I was taught to share and I
mean this weren't you taught to share
now it's like you want to be part of the
American dream you can remember you can
come here have a piece of the pie now
you don't even get a the pie now you
don't even get the plate the crumbs you
got to watch the dishes right so I would
I would think if I was a teacher do we
have any teachers here yes she said that
like I'm so done teaching I am so done
teaching I'm telling you we I would
teach if I was teaching kindergarten I
would teach greed to kindergarten kids
to get them ready for this Brave New
World I be okay kids we're going to play
a fun game it's called dog eat dog world
with a
d now Johnny you have two fruit rollups
why well my mom says I should share well
your mom is stupid I want you to hold on
to these Fruit Roll-Ups and I want you
to steal all of Sally's
cookies but that's mean no Johnny that's
America and Sally I want you to stop
crying cuz I want you to go into Timmy's
book bag and take some of zeroll not all
of it CU he needs to focus but enough to
kill your appetite wash it down with the
chocolate milk and with the remainder of
pills I want you to sell them to Donna
after you call her a lazy Pig
but Don is my best friend no kids Cold
Hard Cash is your best friend with a c
you got that cold hard cash and I want
you to learn all these skills otherwise
you're going to wind up with a student
loan debt that you're never going to be
able to pay with some useless college
degrees that you're never going to be
able to use working in an electronic
sweatsh shot living in your parents
basement eating Doritos watching video
games waiting to
die just want to
I love the kids I just want to throw it
out I'm available for children's
parties I do want to say we got to start
talking to each other we got the mask
off right everyone too much with the
Emojis the Texas the No One Look looking
right no one even like everyone
everything's an emoji you know what's
going to happen we're going to start to
turn into really bad mes it's like I
heard your father was in the
hospital but he's getting out in a
couple weeks
tell them I love
him kissy
face but I was I was listening to
YouTube the other
day and mcjagger was in concert and he
was like he was getting really angry at
everybody he was he was like he was
flipping out was like everybody put your
cell phones down put them down and look
at me you spend $3,000 for a ticket just
to see me and you got your cell phones
techn techology was supposed to make us
closer but it's tearing us apart you go
to a restaurant you don't even talk to
each other you talk to the food anyway
I'm angry I wrote a song I did and it
goes something like
this ooh my self is
string went B just
today if I don't take a
selfie oh yeah I'm going to fade
away oh
Instagram it's just a click away it's
just a click away
oh
Internet it's just a click away it's
just a click away
[Applause]
yeah ooh I hate my
cooking I always eat
paet if I don't get some food now oh
yeah I'm going to fade
away oh Grub
Hub it's just a click away I need some
food today dating sell
ABS it's just a flick away I need a girl
today y
[Music]
yeah thank you everybody you've been
awesome good
night